♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Peter, come on.
- What?
- We're starting.
Oh, is this, uh, a new one?
I thought it was a rerun.
Okay, here we go.
Line?
What are those guys doing over there?
Hey, what are those
guys doing over there?
I added a "hey."
Here we go, Patriots!
All right, now let's go miss the urinal
with half a whiz and get out of here.
Right on!
Hey, why you guys leaving?
We're taking a party bus to the game.
A bus for partying?
Aw, that sounds awesome.
Like a pair of Pete's Headphones.
♪ Oye c├│mo va ♪
♪ Mi ritmo ♪
♪ Bueno pa' gozar ♪
♪ Mulata ♪
♪ Ba, ba-da ba-da-da ♪
♪ Ba-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da... ♪
Mom, can we eat?
My stomach is starting to sound
like Arnold Schwarzenegger
gasping for air at the
end of Total Recall.
My eyes are
popping out at the end of this movie!
Well, I'd like to wait for your father.
L-Let me send him another
infuriating check-in text.
Hel-lo!
Yes?
Peter, where the hell have you been?
On a magical journey to
Gillette Stadium and back.
You remember last night
when you called me
the lowest-class alcoholic in the world?
Well, I found one rung lower.
I'm a party bus guy now.
That's got to be way better
than when I drove a Fiat.
Hey! You cut me off!
What? Turn down your radio.
I can't. My stomach's pressed
up against the dial.
You want to go?
Get me 17 shoehorns and some canola oil,
and we'll go!
Get back here!
Okay, guys, now this is a bus
for a fireman's bachelor party.
So just follow my lead
and we'll fit right in.
All right!
9/11! Boston Strong!
Never forget!
How about this guy? You forget?
No way. You're too Boston
Strong to ever forget.
Let's roll!
Uh, I mean... civil servants
with hero complexes!
Boom!
- All right!
- Welcome, other firefighters.
Bring us the man of the hour.
Come on, Smitty!
To my last night as a free man!
Hmm. Unfortunate timing.
Now, which one of these scumbag firemen
will go after his fianc├йe?
Already happened. We're very happy.
♪ Firemen are not good friends ♪
♪ They'll bang your wife
when you are dead. ♪
Peter, this sucks!
What are we doing out here?
_
I'm beginning to think
those vodka cranberries
may have had alcohol in them.
Wow, partying on the bus to prom.
Doesn't get much cooler than this.
None of these lame kids is drinking.
Eh, I think I know what's going on.
Hey, how many of you kids
are on the horny drugs?
I'm a cop.
But I'm not a narc.
Cool cop! Cool cop! Cool cop!
Did you dook yourself?
Just listen to the chant, Peter.
Listen to the chant.
_
Close dancing, 12 o'clock.
Hey, arm's length, dirty porno lovers!
So, going stag tonight, Meg?
Oh, no, I brought someone.
Hello. I'm in love with Meg.
Well, now I'm very sorry I asked.
Wow, the end of high school.
Tonight, we pass around Stifler's mom,
and in the morning, it's off
to die quick in Vietnam.
Peter, I think you're getting
your movies mixed up.
Attention, students.
It's time to announce this
year's prom king and queen.
Natalee Holloway!
Now, now.
And the winners are...
Connie D'Amico and "Kermit Legs" Kyle!
Ah, so close.
Hello, gorgeous.
- How old are you?
- 18.
All right, and I just
recorded you saying that.
And hi. I am Glenn Quagmire.
Courtney. Nice to meet you.
You don't look like
you're in high school.
I got held back. You
like getting held back?
Sometimes.
All right, youngins.
I dragged this piece of dirty
cardboard in from the alley
to show y'all how to get down.
Peter! Let's boogie!
♪ Ho! Ho! ♪
Aah! There was a staple in the box!
Where's the nurse's office?
Hey, you want to get out of here?
Yeah. Let's go.
You take requests?
What are you looking for?
♪ A-hunga, hunga, hunga, hunga... ♪
♪ It's been one week
since you looked at me ♪
♪ Cocked your head to the
side and said I'm angry ♪
♪ Five days since you laughed at me... ♪
I know all the lyrics.
- I just don't know them fast!
- ♪ Three days... ♪
- And initial here.
- What is all this?
Oh, these just say if anything
should happen to you,
I'm not responsible, blah-blah-blah.
I'm-I'm just boring myself.
I had a lot of fun with
you tonight, Courtney.
Me too.
Oh, Courtney.
Oh, Glenn.
Oh, oh, giggity!
Wait. Did you just say "giggity"?
Yeah. Sorry.
Sometimes I just blurt that
out when I get excited.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
_
Here. Rub this up and down
on the inside of your cheek.
- Giggity.
- Aah! Stop saying that!
_
What is it, Glenn? What's wrong?
You're... you're my daughter!
Oh, my God!
Wow.
I guess this means I have
a phone call to make.
Hey, it's Glenn Quagmire.
Would you tell Andrew that
he is not the father?
Andrew, you are not the father.
Courtney, there's something
I just got to ask.
What the heck was the
theme of that dance?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, like,
there was palm trees like it was Hawaii,
but then there was a suit
of armor in the corner.
There was a big banner
w-with fish on it.
Can we get back to the
fact that you're my dad?
Yeah, you're right.
I'm-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Well, let me ask. What's
up with your mom?
Actually, I never knew my mom.
I was hoping that you
could tell me about her.
Uh... of course I can.
Your mom...
your mom... was really...
thing hanging on the
bulletin board behind you.
That's so nice to hear. Tell me more.
Oh, gosh, she was, she was just so...
word on the bottom of your coffee cup.
I always knew she would be! What else?
I just have some great
memories of her...
numbers to call in case of emergency
or accidental poisoning.
It's like she's here with us right now.
So you don't know your
mom? Who do you live with?
Well, right now I'm on a futon
in the rafters of my friend's garage.
Oh! Actually, I better get going.
I have to feed their
ferrets. They breed them.
It's pretty terrifying.
Anyway, thank you so
much for being so nice,
and let's talk soon?
Wait, hold on. You can't
live in a ferret garage.
You need a home.
You know, you could move in here.
I have an extra bedroom,
and the bed has a bunch
of different-sized pillows on it.
Hmm. I do love dealing with
those pillows every day,
but are you sure?
I don't want to be a burden.
No, it's no problem.
Hey, you're my daughter.
I want to make sure you
have everything you need.
Thanks. That's sweet.
Um... okay! Yeah. I'll move in.
That's huge for me.
Hey, is that an Instant Pot?
- No, it's a Crock-Pot.
- You got to get an Instant Pot.
You can make short ribs in
it. It falls right off...
Yeah, yeah, falls right
off the bone. I know.
I've had this conversation five times.
Hey, Quagmire.
I hear you're considering
an Instant Pot.
Courtney, that's Joe, my neighbor.
Hey, Courtney. You getting
this guy on board?
So, I think I had a wet
nightmare last night.
Is that possible?
- Hello, fellow daddios.
- Did you bang your kid yet?
Okay, Peter, can I talk
to you for a second?
I'm sorry, but I am not going
to stand for any misogyny.
Stop acting like a Neanderthal pig.
Those sound scary.
What were you two ladies talking about?
Joe, can I talk to you for a second?
It's 2019. Time-tested jokes like that
are now offensive and not funny at all.
Okay, I got to go.
I'm taking Courtney to
her first WNBA game.
I got courtside seats.
They're way in the back, but
I'm sitting next to Courtney.
I-I got dad jokes now.
See you, friends.
Yes, 911?
Someone has stolen the old Quagmire
and replaced him with a respectable man.
Sir, this line is reserved
for emergencies only.
Please end your clammy joke.
Okay. Sorry.
- You remember what I told you?
- I'm the best around.
Nothing's gonna ever keep me down.
That's right. I made that up.
Now go get 'em, kiddo.
I'll be watching with the other moms.
Here's all the usual suspects.
Oh, you're doing a video.
Turn it... G-Get it off.
Glenn, I look terrible.
Glenn, Courtney's up!
Okay, okay, here we go. Please.
Let's go, Courtney!
Ah, perfect! That's a ten!
9.2? 9.2?!
9.2?!
9.2?! I'll give you a 9.2.
On the Richter scale!
Courtney, let's go.
I get to go again. We do it twice.
Oh.
Let's go, Courtney.
So, you liking Take Your
Daughter to Work Day?
Uh, yeah!
I can't believe my dad knows
how to fly this thing.
- You want to try?
- Me? I don't know.
Come on, it's easy.
You don't even need a college degree,
which is a very scary
true fact. Go ahead.
You're doing great. Now roll it.
What? No way.
Don't worry, you're a Quagmire.
It's in your blood.
- Grip it and rip it.
- Okay.
Attagirl. Perfect.
N-No. No, no. We're not doing that.
I got my daughter with
me today, you perverts.
He's not doing it today.
- Aw, shoot.
- Another time.
Probably got his kid with him.
I'm glad you guys could
finally come over for dinner.
Sure thing, Lois. Thanks for having us.
See, Meg? That's a thigh gap.
Now, Courtney, I'd like to
awkwardly introduce you
to someone your own age.
Courtney, this is Megan.
Maybe you listen to the same music.
- Hey.
Yo, Courtney, what's your Instagram?
I just got on there and
need some interesting peeps
- to follow.
- Oh, you'll have to ask my dad.
He approves all my follow requests.
Denied! Nice try, ass.
Hey, have you guys seen
the Wonder Woman film?
- Yeah, no.
- Oh, you have to.
It's a triumph.
Courts and I have seen it five times.
It's an important movie, Peter.
You should watch it with
Meg. It's a masterwork.
Oh, I've been wanting to see that.
Okay, we totally will.
Hey, Dad, I just checked the weather,
and it looks like sunny
skies all weekend.
You guys have big plans?
Yeah, we're going camping.
Hey, you and Meg should
come with us, Peter.
We'll make it a father-daughter
bonding weekend.
- Oh, that's a great idea.
- Yeah, let's go, Dad.
Y-You know who you should
take instead of me?
Uh, Stewie or-or Chris or Brian.
May-Maybe Lois.
Or Seamus is fun.
Carter Pewterschmidt,
Babs Pewterschmidt,
Bonnie, Joe, their son Kevin,
Cleveland, Jerome, Bruce, Opie, Carl,
the "phony" guy, the
ostrich, Al Harrington,
Billy Finn, John Travolta
from one of our cutaways,
uh, all of our characters
as Star Wars characters,
everybody from The Cleveland Show,
Cherry Chevapravatdumrong...
that's how that name is pronounced...
the Orville... the ship, not the cast...
um, me... Aw, damn it!
Okay, fine. I'll go.
- Thank you.
- Cool.
I heard my name, too. I'm in!
No? I'll drive, buy snacks?
No? Okay.
Everyone else is out here, too.
Oh, my God, it's literally everyone.
That can only mean... show ghosts!
_
I'm really glad you decided to bring Meg
on this camping trip, Peter.
- It's gonna be great.
- Because we're in the...
Because we're in the great outdoors.
Ah.
You don't get air like this
back in Quahog, do you, Pete?
Uh, I don't know. Some places, probably.
Hoo-ah! Gosh, being in nature
gives me such great energy.
Hey, Courtney, you ever see
a yellow-headed warbler?
That's the only warbler I haven't seen.
Not for long it's not.
Don't answer that. We're eating.
They're probably eating.
Okay, we're gonna have a
fun camp competition.
And the first event, worth five points,
is a race down to the lake right now!
Last one there is a stinky poo-poo egg!
Come on, Dad!
What Meg didn't know,
what none of them knew,
is that I already was
a stinky poo-poo egg.
Boy, you don't get stars like this
back in Quahog, do you, Pete?
Stop calling me Pete.
I know what'll cheer you up. Skits!
♪ Skits, skits, skits, skits ♪
♪ Skits-skits-skits-skits, skits-skits ♪
♪ Skits! ♪
Well, isn't this a
perfect bench for a sit.
Say, Dad, what are you doing?
Oh, just sitting on the invisible bench,
reading about those
North Korea jokesters.
But, Dad, they moved the
invisible bench last week.
Oh. It's over there now.
Whoa!
Ladies and gentlemen, "The
Invisible Bench" skit.
Peter, you're up.
Okay, here's one. I call
it "The Invisible Noose."
First, I throw a rope
over this tree limb,
put the noose around my neck.
Now I'll just step onto this rock
and jump off into the
sweet relief of death.
Peter, would you mind
flattening your rod?
Fine. I'll Tootsie it between my thighs.
Yeah, okay, whatever gets it
away from my daughter's face.
Are you eating an apple with a knife?
God, that's always so forced.
Hold on. We've been here already.
Yeah, she's right.
That's where I graffitied that rock.
_
We've changed our minds.
We're going on record.
We're not lost, all right?
We're just two dads bonding
with our daughters,
and getting lost is
not part of the plan.
All right, nobody panic.
We just need to get our bearings.
Hey, here comes a hiker.
Excuse me, sir, we're lost.
Ha! Then you must be my car keys, right?
It is so nice to get out of the city
and meet friendly people.
You're not helping, Dad. As usual.
Well, at least I didn't get us lost.
We're not lost! We're just...
two dads in the woods,
who love our daughters very, very much.
Okay, so maybe it's not
the life we chose.
Well, you chose it. I didn't.
That's for damn sure!
- Dad, will you help him?
- Shh.
I've been waiting for this.
I knew it was fake.
Dad, I'm sorry. I didn't...
I'm not Dad! I'm Quagmire!
Glenn Quagmire!
Giggity giggity!
I don't want to be out
here! I hate camping!
And what the hell was the
theme of that stupid prom?!
All the cups said, "Oh, What a Night!"
I mean, if it was, "Oh,
What a Knight" with a "K,"
that would've made some sense,
'cause there was a suit of armor there.
What was that about? Answer me!
I-I think it's possible to
overthink these things.
Ugh, what a mish-mosh.
Damn it, I just want to be home,
not here, lost in the woods,
looking at this stupid map
with a magnifying glass.
Aah!
Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
- Help!
- Dear God, someone help us!
You know when this would never happen?
If I was sitting on the
couch, watching TV,
ignoring you completely.
Courtney, I'm sorry for
what I said earlier.
You mean when you completely
ripped my school dance theme?
No, no, there was no theme to rip.
That's the point. I
stand by all of that.
If anything, I'm more angry.
No, I'm-I'm talking
about being your father
before I was ready.
I promise, if we make it out of here,
we can start again.
- Deal?
- Deal.
9/11!
Boston Strong!
Oh, it's Smitty.
We're saved!
But we should warn the
birds the fire's coming.
All right, stay calm.
Grab the pictures. I'll
get your mother's ashes.
Wow, Peter, that was a
close call with that fire,
but I'm glad you all made
it back safe and sound.
Yeah, me, too.
What the hell?
Oh, I hope it's okay.
I bought some more pillows.
I mean, what is the deal
with women and pillows?
Has-has anyone else noticed this?
No.
No one?
But I-I got three minutes
of material on pillows.
We don't want to hear it.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.tv